<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>JOMS :: 나를 위한 논문 요약</title><link>https://kurette683.github.io/joms/index.html</link><description>Journal of Oral and Maxillofacial Surgery (JOMS)의 최신 논문 목록입니다.</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>ko-kr</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 06:57:19 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://kurette683.github.io/joms/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>20250703</title><link>https://kurette683.github.io/joms/20250703/index.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 06:57:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kurette683.github.io/joms/20250703/index.html</guid><description>20250703 발표 논문 목록 아래 목록에서 논문 제목을 클릭하여 내용을 확인하세요.
Guidelines for the Management of Patients With Orofacial Pain and Temporomandibular Disorders July 2025 AAOMS News and Announcements Masthead Oral Maxillofacial Surgery Residency Programs: It Is Time for Open and Clear Parental Leave Policies RE: “Coronectomy in Lower Third Molar Surgery: A Systematic Review and Meta-analysis” RE: Does Combining Arthrocentesis With Injectable Platelet-Rich Fibrin Outperform Arthrocentesis or Injectable Platelet-Rich Fibrin Alone in Alleviating Pain and Improving Function in Temporomandibular Joint Dysfunction? RE: Patterns of Orbital Fractures Caused by Sports Injuries in Children RE: Timing a Surgeon’s Retirement: Balancing Experience With Age-Related Decline Resident Wellness in Oral and Maxillofacial Surgery: Can We Do Better? The Use of Clear Aligners for Orthognathic Surgery: A Systematic Review What Color Is Your Grass? A Half-Century Review of Male and Female Resident Outcomes in Oral and Maxillofacial Surgery: A Single-Institution Report Adenotonsillectomy Reduces Obstructive Sleep Apnea and Improves Sleep Quality in Adult Patients Association Between Type of Residency Interview, Virtual Versus In-Person, and Distance From Applicants' Dental School to Oral and Maxillofacial Surgery Program Matched: Report From the American Association of Oral and Maxillofacial Surgeons Committee on Education and Training Comparison of Autogenous Tooth Graft With Polylactic Co-Glycolic Acid in Postextraction Socket for Alveolar Ridge Preservation: A Randomized Control Trial Does Discectomy and Reconstruction With Viable Osteochondral and Umbilical Allografts Reduce Pain and Improve Function for Intra-Articular Pain and Dysfunction? Does Lingual Frenotomy Improve Breastfeeding in Newborns With Ankyloglossia? A Randomized Controlled Trial How Artificial Intelligence Differs From Humans in Peer Review Is Abobotulinum A Superior to Onabotulinum A in Reducing Pain in Patients With Nocturnal Bruxism? Is Low-Level Laser Treatment Effective in Reducing Pain, Swelling, and Trismus After Removing Impacted Maxillary and Mandibular Third Molars? Is Postoperative Steroid Use Associated With Improved Outcomes in Severe Odontogenic Infections? Open Versus Closed Management for Gunshot Wounds of the Mandible – Which More Frequently Achieves Satisfactory Bony Union? A Systematic Review and Meta-Analysis Outcomes of Different Internal Fixation Strategies for Double Mandibular Fractures: A Systematic Review and Meta-analysis Pre-emptive Montelukast and Its Effect on Clinical Outcomes After Mandibular Third Molar Surgery: A Triple-blinded Randomized Controlled Trial A Novel Bipartite 3D Printed CAD/CAM Splint for Treatment of Mandibular Fractures Alveoloplasty: A Paradigm Shift to a More Efficient Surgical Technique Autografts, Bone Substitutes, and Combined Approaches for Secondary Alveolar Bone Grafting: A Systematic Review and Meta-Analysis Computed Tomography–Based Predictors of Difficult Intubation in Oral and Maxillofacial Surgery Patients Deep-Learning Method for the Diagnosis and Classification of Orbital Blowout Fracture Based on Computed Tomography Nonlinear Cutting Guides in Oral and Maxillofacial Surgery: A Technical Note Outcomes of Pediatric Maxillofacial Giant Cell Lesion Management in Syndromic Versus Nonsyndromic Patients: A 21-Year Review Risk Factors Associated With Complications in Treated Mandibular Fractures: A Retrospective Cohort Study Comparison of Panoramic Radiography and Cone Beam Computed Tomography for Lower Third Molar Assessment Among Different Dental Specialists Complication Rates of the Anterior Iliac Crest Bone Graft Donor Site for 426 Pediatric Patients Undergoing Alveolar Bone Grafting Cost-Effectiveness Analysis of Immediate Tissue Engineering Bone Graft Versus Fibula-Free Flap Reconstruction for Mandibular Continuity Defects Secondary to Benign Pathology Does Suction Catheter-Guided Nasotracheal Intubation Reduce Nasal Bleeding? Patient-Specific Titanium Implants Reduce Hardware-Related Complications Compared to Stock Reconstruction Plates for Virtually Guided Fibular Free Flaps in Head and Neck Reconstruction The Effect of Le Fort I Osteotomy on Nasal Tip Rotation in Dynamic Smile The Shield-Like Septal Extension Graft: A Novel Technique for Nasal Tip Management in Revision Rhinoplasty Bevacizumab-Conjugated Curcumin Nanoparticles Promote Cytotoxicity and Apoptosis in Human Malignant Oral Keratinocytes In Vitro Concentrated Growth Factor Constructs Improve Wound Healing After Third Molar Surgery: A Split-Mouth Randomized Controlled Trial Effect of Photobiomodulation on the Control of Edema and Pain After Third Molar Surgery: Double-Blinded Randomized Clinical Trial Enhanced Recovery After Orthognathic Surgery: Evidence Synthesis for Postoperative Care Is Intra-articular Injection of Hyaluronic Acid, Corticosteroid or Platelet-rich Plasma Following Medical Ozone Superior to Medical Ozone Alone in the Treatment of Temporomandibular Joint Osteoarthritis? Minimizing Chairside Conversion and Lab Work for Full Arch Restorations—A Technique Note Systemic Melatonin Improves Regeneration After Facial Nerve Crush Injury in a Rat Model The Effects of Different Bimaxillary Orthognathic Surgery Sequencing on the Temporomandibular Joint Space of Skeletal Class II Malocclusion Patients Association of Preoperative Nutritional Status With Outcomes in Fronto-Orbital Advancement for Syndromic Craniosynostosis Chondroid Diffuse Tenosynovial Giant Cell Tumor of the Temporomandibular Joint: A Case of a Rare Maxillofacial Tumor With Unique Pathophysiology and Therapeutic Considerations Comparison of Occlusion Using Conventional Versus Virtual Model Surgery in Segmental Maxillary Orthognathic Surgery Using the American Board of Orthodontics Discrepancy Index Do Healing Rates Differ Between Medication-Related and Medication-Unrelated Osteonecrosis of the Jaw? Emerging Point of the Infratrochlear Nerve With Reference to the Nasion and Its Clinical Implications in Craniofacial Surgery Is Treatment at a Level 1 Trauma Center Associated With Better Outcomes in Adults With Isolated Midface Fractures? What Factors Influence Success of Mandibular Reconstructions With Patient-Specific Selective Laser Melted Reconstruction Plates? Body Mass Index (BMI) Changes and Muscle Loss After Orthognathic Surgery: A Prospective Study Characterization of Tenosynovial Giant Cell Giant Cell Tumors in the Temporomandibular Joint: A Multidisciplinary Approach to Treatment DOES THE HYALURONIC ACID DOSAGE DURING ARTHROCENTESIS INFLUENCE PAIN REDUCTION AND MAXIMAL INCISAL OPENING? How Does Thrombocytopenia Affect Outcomes in Head and Neck Cancer Surgery with Free Flap Reconstruction? Is Handheld Ultrasonography Reliable as a Primary Imaging Modality for the Diagnosis of Internal Derangement and Degenerative Joint Disease of the Temporomandibular Joint? Rapid and Low-Cost Mesh Shaping Technique for Orbital Fracture Reconstruction – A Technical Note Evaluation of the radiological results between local and coronal incisions in the treatment of zygomaticomaxillary complex fractures</description></item></channel></rss>